[
  {
    "id": "149c0cb6-2389-4045-b78e-877836143247",
    "question": "Which trait contributes more to being a successful manager?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I think good organization skills contribute more to being a successful manager\nThis skill is necessary to keep the project on track and achieve success\nLast year I participated in a team project. We had a lot of work to do but luckily our team leader had a good organizational skill. He was good at arranging schedules, good at setting the plans, making deadlines. All we had to do was follow his schedules, and listen to his advice. Our project was successful. Although most of our team members were newbies, we didn't have much experience and knowledge. Thanks to our team leader's organizational skills, we were successful.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T08:30:39.837Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "41022e19-c9bd-494a-8868-9a6933ae528b",
    "question": "Do you think it's important to try new ideas to become successful leader?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I think it's important to try new ideas to become successful leader\nIt's a good way to attract customers and earn profits.\nLast year, I opened a restaurant. Even though I worked really hard, I didn't have many customers. I was disappointed but I didn't give up. I came up with new ideas. I created new menu items such as spicy chicken, sweet and sour chicken and so on. Actually my customers liked them. They came to my store. Gradually I have got a lot of regular customers and earned a lot of money. My business has become successful.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T08:32:07.322Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "a1845412-e8a6-4a1d-a4de-a1a3d3d7aba4",
    "question": "Which of the following traits is the most valuable in a coworker?\nGood communication skills\nFriendliness\nTalent",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I think good communication skills are the most valuable in a coworker\nMost tasks require members to interact with each other effectively (tương tác với nhau hiệu quả) to reach a common goal (đạt được mục tiêu chung). As a result, the work productivity will increase.\nI am currently working in the marketing department. Every time we have a team project, we often have many meetings. Although each member has different background and experience, we have good communication skills. We try to present ideas clearly and listen to others carefully. We hardly have any miscommunication and misunderstanding (hiểu nhầm). As a result, our team projects are always successful.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T08:33:08.066Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "22737c7f-9704-4ef5-979e-3fc7d137e0ea",
    "question": "Which is the most important for an employee?\nPast working experience\nRecommendation\nEducational backgrounds",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I think past working experience is the most important for an employee\nExperienced employees can adapt to new environment (thích nghi với môi trường mới) quickly compared inexperienced one. Sometimes, they can handle responsibilities (đảm đương trách nhiệm) and solve the problem effectively based on their previous experience. Also, companies can save their resources in terms of (liên quan tới) training and minimize loss. For example, recently, my company just hired a new salesperson. Since he has 4 years of experience, he can easily handle all tasks (xử lý nhiệm vụ) and seek (tìm kiếm) new customers for our company.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T08:40:20.043Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "a754970a-d339-47bb-8d43-544c5ea0cee8",
    "question": "Which of the following ways is more effective to learn new skills as an employee?\nReading a book or a manual\nTaking an online lecture\nLearning from other colleagues",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I think learning from other colleagues is more effective to learn new skills as an employee\nThey can provide practical insights (kiến thức thực tế) that may not be found in books or lectures\nLast year I got a job in marketing department. At first, I was a newbie. I didn't have any experience. I didn't know what to do. Luckily, I met a nice colleague at that company. He taught me many things. He gave me lots of tips and advice. Thanks to him, I can learn new skills. I was able to perform my work better (thực hiện công việc tốt hơn).",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T08:41:34.959Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "b9c67d54-821f-4a12-8a7d-3e43c9a5b428",
    "question": "Which is better to learn new skills? One on one from supervisor or group training?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I think one-on-one training is better to learn new skills\nIt's more interactive (có tính tương tác) and effective\nLast year I got a job in marketing department of ABC company. At first, I was a newbie. I didn't know what to do. But luckily I met a very nice supervisor. He had a lot of experience and knowledge. He was really kind. He was willing to help me. He taught me many things. He gave me a lot of tips and advice. Sometimes, he even stayed after work to train me. I was really thankful for him. I was able to learn from his one-on-one training. After a month, I was able to perform better.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T08:45:10.221Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "c7e890ab-5d21-4c88-b9f3-1d45ab8e62f5",
    "question": "If a company is making a major decision, do you think it would be better to allow one leader to decide or ask a group of people for their ideas?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I believe ask a group of people for their ideas would be better if a company is making a major decision\nTeam members come from diverse backgrounds (nền tảng đa dạng), experiences, and expertise so they can provide comprehensive and innovative solutions (giải pháp sáng tạo và toàn diện) to reach a good decision.\nLast year I participated in a big project. There were 5 people in our team. We had to make an important decision but everyone had different ideas and opinions. So, we had a lot of meetings and we shared a lot of ideas. Eventually, we were able to reach an agreement and make a good decision. Thanks to everyone's ideas, the project was successful.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T08:48:23.574Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "d2f9128e-67a3-4fa7-b43e-5962c46d789a",
    "question": "Is it important to get everyone's agreement to reach a final decision?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I don't think it is important to get everyone's agreement to reach a final decision\nLast year I graduated from college and got a job in the marketing department. There were many team projects. One day I participated in an important project. Actually we had to make an advertisement so we had a lot of meetings. During the meetings, we discussed the project. However, we had different ideas and opinions. One day an idea was proposed. Some people agreed, some people disagreed but we did it anyway. After a month, the result came out. Fortunately, our project was successful.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T08:51:17.309Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "e5a143bf-98c2-4d6b-8f1a-3715d48b8c7e",
    "question": "Which of the following traits do you need to display to a corporation when applying to it?\nCommunication skills/ good time management/ passion for the industry.",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I think it is important I need to display good communication skills to a corporation when applying to it.\nMost tasks require members to interact with each other effectively (tương tác hiệu quả) to reach a common goal (đạt được mục tiêu chung) so recruiters tend to hire candidates with good communication skills\nLast year I participated in an interview. The interviewers asked me a lot of questions. I tried to listen to them carefully and present my answers clearly. Eventually I got an offer from this company. Now I'm working in the marketing department. Thanks to good communication skills, there is hardly any misunderstanding and miscommunication with my coworkers.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T08:54:42.618Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "f8d67b35-1c49-4e57-9f2a-48e9bd5cb3a2",
    "question": "Which of the following abilities do you think is the most important when working in a company?\nBeing good at teamwork\nProblem solving skills\nFast learning skills",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I think the most important ability when working in a company is problem solving skills. This is because problems can arise/happen (phát sinh/xảy ra) anytime so if the employees have this skill, they can improve their work performance.\nLast year I worked as a customer service agent. One day I had to deal with a problem with my customers. I was a newbie and I didn't know what to do. Luckily, I had a coworker who had great problem-solving skills. He was able to analyze the situation, identify the issue, and propose the solution (phân tích tình huống, xác dịnh vấn đề, đề xuất giải pháp) based on the experience. He gave me a lot of tips and advice. Thanks to his suggestions, I knew how to handle that task effectively.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T08:57:31.892Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "07e452a8-942f-4b8d-a45c-68f3d7c9b742",
    "question": "Do you agree or disagree that having a sense of humor is an important trait to have when looking for a job?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I disagree that having a sense of humor is an important trait to have when looking for a job\nA humorous candidate may create a comfortable atmosphere (tạo môi trường thoải mái) and leave a good impression on the recruiters (để lại ấn tượng tốt với nhà tuyển dụng). However, if they tell jokes or funny stories inappropriately, it may be counterproductive (phản tác dụng). In addition, companies tend to find someone who can perform effectively at work so they will prioritize those with extensive experience and skills like communication skills or problem-solving skills. Recently, my company hired an IT programmer. Although he is very serious, he is skilled at programming and dealing with big projects.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T09:01:14.526Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "18c9d647-35a3-4fbe-8b91-57b2de67c934",
    "question": "Do you agree or disagree that it's important to be able to adapt to a new situation at work where you are familiar with other things?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I agree that it's important to be able to adapt to a new situation at work where I am familiar with other things\nThey can respond effectively to changes in your work environment and learn new skills to improve their work productivity\nTwo years ago, I worked in the accounting department. I was quite familiar with (quen với) all the tasks and software. One day, my company decided to change the software. At first, I felt overwhelmed (cảm thấy choáng ngợp). But I tried to join some workshops to learn how to use it. I also ask my coworkers for help. Thanks to the adaptability (khả năng thích nghi), I can easily get used to (quen với) new software. I can perform better.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T09:04:23.147Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "29d8f731-4e6c-4f9d-beac-46a5d7c98e53",
    "question": "What are some disadvantages of starting your own business rather being employed at a company?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: Starting up has many drawbacks. First, when people start a business, they have to handle all aspects of the business such as finance, marketing, operations, and human resources. This would require them to spend much time at work and leave them little time (để lại ít thời gian) with their personal relationships. Eventually, they may suffer from (hứng chịu) stress, depression, and so on. Also, if they don't have good financial management skills or the market environment is unfavorable (không thuận lợi), they might face financial loss (gặp thua lỗ) or even go bankrupt (phá sản). Meanwhile, when working for someone else, they just need to complete assigned tasks (nhiệm vụ được giao) and receive monthly salaries.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T09:07:35.780Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "3a5b8916-57d5-4c0e-b3da-35f6d7d98f62",
    "question": "Who has a great influence on you when selecting a job?\nCollege professors/ Parents/ Friends",
    "answer": "Sample 1: College professors have a great influence on you when selecting a job? \nThey can provide insights to help me land a job (kiếm 1 công việc) effectively\nWhen I was a senior in college, I participated in many interviews. But I failed every time. I was disappointed and didn't know what to do. So I met my professor named Tim. He had lots of experience and knowledge. He was very skillful and wise. He listened to me carefully. He gave me a lot of tips and advice. He recommended that I participate in an internship program. I followed his advice (làm theo lời khuyên). I was able to learn many things there. After the internship program, I was hired. Thanks to my professor, I was able to get a job.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T09:10:48.413Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "4b6c9a05-6807-4d1d-9ce4-42476e8a9f71",
    "question": "Do you agree or disagree that salary is more important than the work field for employees to have higher satisfaction about their work?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I agree that salary is more important than the work field for employees to have higher satisfaction about their work. \nIt's necessary to have a higher salary to make a living (kiếm sống)\nFor example, 5 years ago I worked at ABC company which was a small company. I liked the work field but the problem was the salary was quite low. I wasn't able to make a living. After paying for the rent, buying some food, I didn't have any left. So I wasn't able to save some money. Eventually I quit the job and move to XYZ company. Currently I'm working there. I'm getting higher salary. After paying for the rent, buying food and paying for the car insurance, I still have some money. So I save up to get ready for the future. I'm much satisfied with my job because I feel safe about my future.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T09:14:02.259Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "5c7d0b12-7918-4e2e-a0f5-58587f9ba080",
    "question": "Do you prefer to work at home or at a company?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I prefer to work at a company\nWorking at a company, people can interact directly with their coworkers, which would enhance their work productivity. Meanwhile, working at home may be distracting.\nDuring the Covid-19, I had to work at home. Unfortunately. There were many distractions such as TV, computers and so on. I wasn't able to focus on my work. Sometimes, I missed the deadline. Nowadays I go to the office. There is no TV, no distractions. I can fully focus on my work. Also, there are many coworkers who are very experienced. Whenever I have the problems, I can ask for their help. It's very helpful. Overall, it's good for work efficiency.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T09:17:15.894Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "6d8e1c23-8a29-4f3f-b1f6-697698abc889",
    "question": "How could a company most effectively improve its employees' health?\nAllowing daily exercise breaks\nProviding healthy food\nOffering workshops or training sessions about health",
    "answer": "Sample 1: A company can improve its employees' health effectively by allowing daily exercise breaks.\nIf employees can work out, they can become healthier. It's a great way to improve work productivity.\nMy team has to handle many projects and we have to work hard day and night, which is really stressful. We always look tired and exhausted. Luckily, my boss hires a Yoga teacher and allows us to have exercise breaks daily. During the breaks, we are able to stretch out our bodies (giãn cơ) and do meditation (thiền). After that, we all feel relaxed and more energetic. We can recharge our batteries. And our work productivity has improved a lot.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T09:20:29.527Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "7e9f2d34-9b3a-4040-c2g7-78869abcdf98",
    "question": "Do you think it is better to let the employees dress freely or have them dress up formally for work?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I think it's better to let the employees dress freely. It's better for their work efficiency.\nLast year, I got a job in the marketing department from ABC company. there I had to wear formal clothes to work. I had to dress up every day. I had to wear tie and suit. It was very uncomfortable. Sometimes it was really hard to move around and breathe in (thở). so in the afternoon, I wasn't able to focus on my work cuz my clothes were so tight, so uncomfortable. On Friday, luckily, we were allowed to wear casually. It was much better. I felt the freedom. It was much easier for me to focus on work.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T09:23:42.160Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "8fa03e45-ac4b-4151-d3h8-89970bcde007",
    "question": "Is it important for companies to evaluate employee's performance?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I think it's important for companies to evaluate employee's performance\nIt's helpful for work productivity of the employees.\nLast year I got a job in marketing department. Unfortunately, I was a newbie. I didn't have any experience. I didn't know what to do. At that time, the company evaluated the employees' work performance. I received a bad evaluation. I was disappointed at myself, so I worked harder and learn harder. As a result, I was able to improve my working skills. After 6 months, I received a better evaluation. And I became highly motivated at work.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T09:26:55.793Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "9gb14f56-bd5c-5262-e4i9-90081cdef116",
    "question": "What are advantages of working an internship before graduating from university?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: Working an internship before graduating from university has many benefits. \nOne of them is that students can gain practical knowledge (đạt được kiến thức thực tế) when handling different tasks at work.\nLast year I participated in an internship program at ABC company. At first, I was a newbie. I didn't have any experience. I didn't know what to do. Luckily, I met a senior at that company. He taught me many things. I was able to do lots of things during my internship. Now I got a job from XYZ company. Although it is my first full-time job, I can work better because I learned many things from my internship program. I can help my team members.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T09:30:09.426Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "10hc25g67-ce6d-6373-f5j0-01192defg225",
    "question": "Do you think an open office with co-workers or a private space offers the best environment?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I think an open office with co-workers offers the best environment \nEmployees can interact with each other directly and improve communication. This would be helpful for work productivity.\nLast year I graduated from college and got a job in marketing department. At that time, I was a newbie, I didn't have any experience. I didn't know what to do for the team project. I wasn't able to help my team members. But luckily, I worked in an open office with my coworkers. They had lots of experience and expertise. They were willing to help me. Whenever I had a question, I asked for their help. I asked for tips and advice. I was able to work with them, spend time with them. It was very helpful to finish the project together. All in all, it was good for my work productivity.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T09:33:22.059Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "11id36h78-df7e-7484-g6k1-12203efgh334",
    "question": "What is more important for employees working at a startup company?\nResponsibility\nIntimacy among coworkers\nPromotion opportunities",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I think responsibility is more important for employees working at a startup company \nStartups typically operate with limited resources (nguồn lực hạn chế), so it's essential for employees to be responsible to handle tasks and challenges. This can contribute to the success of the company.\nA few years ago, I quit my job and started my own business. Actually I opened a chicken restaurant. Luckily, my startup business went well so I decided to hire 2 employees. Although they were very young, they were very responsible. They went to work early to prepare ingredients, set up tables and chairs and only left when everything was cleaned up. They also gave me new ideas to improve our products and services. Thanks to them, my business has become successful and now we can manage to expand my business.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T09:36:35.692Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "12je47i89-eg8f-8595-h7l2-23314fghi443",
    "question": "Do you think business leaders should pay attention to advertising in order to have a successful business? Why?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I think business leaders should pay attention to advertising in order to have a successful business\nAdvertisements can raise public awareness about the products or services and help companies reach target customers. \nLast year I quit my job, and I started my own business. I opened a chicken restaurant. I sold many things such as chicken, beer and so on. I worked hard day and night. However, I didn't have many customers. I was very disappointed, but I didn't give up. I tried to advertise my store on the Internet. I uploaded lots of pictures and reviews. Soon, people saw them and came to my store. Gradually I gained regular customers. Thanks to advertising, I was able to attract more customers. My business became successful.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T09:40:49.325Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "13kf58j90-fh9g-9606-i8m3-34425ghij552",
    "question": "Do you prefer a job which requires travel often or work in an office?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I prefer a job which requires work in an office\nIt's very tiring to travel often for work \nA few years ago, I worked in ABC company. Back then I had to visit many factories. When I went to the factories, it took 5 hours by car. I had to be on the road all the time, so it was very exhausting. And after work I had to return to the office. When I came back to the office, there were more things to do. I was really tired but still I had to stay in the office and work more. It was very tiring. So since then, I only choose a job to work in an office.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T09:43:58.958Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "14lg69k01-gi0h-0717-j9n4-45536hijk661",
    "question": "What are advantages of allowing children to enter museums for free?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: Allowing children to enter museums for free has many benefits\nIt's educational for children\nWhen I was young, there was an art museum near my house. It was free for children so I went there every weekend. There I saw many things such as paintings, drawings and sculptures. Through them, I was able to learn many things about art. Also, there were a lot of workshops which I participated in. I learnt how to draw a painting and learn about sculptures. It was very helpful since I was able to improve my art skills and become interested in art.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T09:47:11.591Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "15mh70l12-hj1i-1828-k0o5-56647ijkl770",
    "question": "Should university students be encouraged to take part in local volunteer activities? Why or why not?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I agree that university students be encouraged to take part in local volunteer activities \nIt's helpful for them to learn how to help others and become a better person. \nWhen I was a freshman, actually I was mean and selfish. I didn't care about others. I was very selfcenter. One the summer break, I participated in local voluntary activities. I went to an animal shelter and helped animals. I fed them, I washed them, I took care of them. Also, I met friends there. We had to work together so I learned how to cooperate with (hợp tác với) others. So through voluntary work, I was able to learn many things and I became a better person, nicer and more considerate.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T09:50:24.224Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "16ni81m23-ik2j-2939-l1p6-67758jklm889",
    "question": "Should students be encouraged in outdoor activities?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I think students should be encouraged in outdoor activities\nIt's helpful for them to become strong and healthy\nWhen I was a student, actually I was weak and shy. I didn't have many friends. I was always alone. One day I participated in an outdoor activity. During PE class, I played soccer with my classmates. At first, I didn't know anything about soccer. But gradually I was able to learn how to play soccer. I was able to learn how to interact with others. I learned team spirit (tinh thần đồng đội). Thanks to this experience, I became outgoing. I was able to make lots of friends. Also, I was able to get rid of stress. As a result, I became healthier and happier.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T09:53:37.857Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "17oj92n34-jl3k-3040-m2q7-78869klmn998",
    "question": "Do you think high school students should learn foreign languages?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I think high school students should learn foreign languages\nFor example, when I was in high school, I learnt many kinds of languages such as English, French and so on. Well, to be honest, I didn't like French so I didn't study hard but I really liked English. I practiced English day and night. I watched a lot of American dramas, I listened to pop songs, I tried to memorize them and practice them and gradually became fluent at speaking English. Last year I went to New York, I met a lot of friends, many foreign friends. We communicated with others in English. So we hung out together all the time. We did many things together such as partying, shopping and so on. Thanks to my English ability, I was able to meet new friends, learn more about the culture.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T09:56:50.490Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "18pk03o45-km4l-4151-n3r8-89970lmno009",
    "question": "Do you agree or disagree that high school students should be obligated to learn how to play a musical instrument?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I disagree that high school students should be obligated to learn how to play a musical instrument\nIt's not necessary\nFor example, when I was in high school, I had to go to school at 8 a.m. in the morning and I had to study until 5 p.m. at school, I had to study so many things such as literature, English, science. On top of that, after school, I had to go to many extensive classes because I had to study hard to get into a good college. There were so many things to do as a high school student. I had to write reports, essays every week. I had to participate in field trips and stuff. I had no time to learn musical instruments. Of course, I loved music so I listened to lots of songs and music but I never learn it. There was no problem.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T10:00:03.123Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "19ql14p56-ln5m-5262-o4s9-90081mnop110",
    "question": "Which of the following can students benefit the most from by studying abroad?\nLearning new cultures\nMeeting new friends\nCareer Opportunities",
    "answer": "Sample 1: Learning new cultures. Students can enhance their cultural understanding\nLast year, I was a senior in college. I didn't have any experience studying abroad. I wasn't familiar with foreign cultures. I decided to go to Japan and study for 1 year. I met lots of Japanese friends. I learned many things about Japan and its culture. I also learned how to speak Japanese. As a result, I was able to understand Japanese culture more. Thanks to this experience, I was able to get a job at a Japanese company.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T10:03:16.756Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "20rm25q67-mo6n-6373-p5t0-01192nopq229",
    "question": "Do you think vending machines in high schools should only sell healthy food?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: It can promote students' health.\nWhen I was in high school, during my first year, there was a vending machine which sold only unhealthy foods such as chocolate, soda and so on. so I ate a lot of unhealthy food every day. Eventually, I gained weight. I became fat and unhealthy. I wasn't happy with it. But one day, the school got rid of all unhealthy food. They started selling healthy food in the vending machine. I was able to eat lots of healthy food such as fruits, nuts, milk. I became healthier. I was able to lose weight.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T10:06:30.389Z"
  },
 {
    "id": "21sn36r78-np7o-7484-q6u1-12203opqr338",
    "question": "Should primary students learn science subjects or art subjects?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I think primary students learn art subjects\nIt's helpful for children's creativity.\nWhen I was in primary school, my parents sent me to an art class. Actually during the class, the teacher taught me how to draw a picture. I was able to express my ideas and myself in the picture. To be honest, I was not talented, but I can manage to draw a picture. Gradually I became interested in art and became more creative. Now I work in the marketing department. Since I have practiced thinking creatively, it's helpful for my work. I am able to produce out of the box ideas and strategies.\n\nSample 2: I think primary students should learn both science and art subjects\nI think primary students should learn both science and art subjects because art will foster their creativity (nuôi dưỡng sự sáng tạo) while science can help them have logical thinking.\nwhen I was a child, my school had an art club as a student who was interested in art in class. I asked my parents permission to join it right away. I also had to learn some science subjects to improve my logical thinking by calculations and technology while I could still spend time for the art club after school and being creative. Now as a designer I can use this knowledge for my job that's why I think both science and art subjects are equally important.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T10:09:44.022Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "22to47s89-oq8p-8595-r7v2-23314pqrs447",
    "question": "What are advantages for high school students to be acting in a theater performance?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I think it's beneficial for high school students to be acting in a theater performance\nWhen I was in high school, actually I was very lonely and shy. I wasn't talkative (nói nhiều) and I didn't have many friends. One day I had to participate in a play and act in a theater performance. At first, I didn't like it. I was scared. I had stage fright (chứng sợ sân khấu). I didn't want to stand in front of other people, classmates and parents. But I practiced a lot, I talked to my classmates and became more and more outgoing, became more confident. I managed to overcome my stage fright. Thanks to this experience, I became more outgoing and confident.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T10:12:57.655Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "23up58t90-pr9q-9606-s8w3-34425qrst556",
    "question": "Do you think primary school students should learn foreign languages or computer skills?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I think primary school students should learn foreign languages\nIt's helpful for them throughout their lives.\nWhen I was 7, I went to America. I started learning English. Because I was young, it was much easier for me to pick up (học) the language and speak English fluently. After a while, I started learning Spanish, Chinese at my early age at primary school. Because I can speak lots of languages, nowadays I can meet lots of foreign friends from all over the world and learn a lot from their experience. It's also easier for me to get a job, especially in foreign companies because they want to hire people who can communicate with people out there.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T10:16:10.288Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "24vq69u01-qs0r-0717-t9x4-45536rstu665",
    "question": "Do you agree with the statement 'being in a class of 20 students is better than being in a class of 5 students'?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I disagree that being in a class of 20 students is better than being in a class of 5 students\nDue to its smaller size, teachers can pay more attention to each student in a class of 5 students. Therefore, students can study more effectively and achieve better learning outcomes/results.\nLast year, I wanted to improve my speaking skills, so I decided to sign up for (đăng kí) a class. At first, I joined a class of 20 students. Because there were many students in the class, I hardly had a chance to practice my speaking skills. I couldn't improve my skills. Then I quit that class and joined a class of smaller size. Although it was expensive, my teacher took care of each student and provided personalized support. Gradually, I can speak English more confidently thanks to my teacher.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T10:19:23.921Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "25wr70v12-rt1s-1828-u0y5-56647stuv774",
    "question": "Do you think teachers should assign a lot of homework to their students?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I think teachers should not assign a lot of homework to their students.\nStudents may feel stressed and overwhelmed to handle all the assignments. This could result in lower learning results. Instead, teachers should focus on quality rather than quantity to ensure students study more effectively.\nWhen I started teaching, I gave my students a lot of assignments. Unfortunately, they always felt tired and exhausted. Then I decided to reduce the amount of homework and design it as a way to complement (bổ sung) in-class lessons. After a while, I noticed that my students' results improved a lot.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T10:22:37.554Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "26xs81w23-su2t-2939-v1z6-67758tuvw883",
    "question": "Which is the best way to get rid of stress?\nWatching TV/ Exercising/ Listening to music",
    "answer": "Sample 1: In my case, exercising is the best way to get rid of stress\nI'm an office worker. I have to work all day. I don't have time to exercise or stretch my body. After work, I have about 3 hours before bed. So I hit the gym (tới phòng tập) at least 2 or 3 times a week to exercise. I run on the treadmill. I lift weights. You know it's exhausting. By doing so, I tend to get rid of stress. It's quite relaxing actually. After exercising, I fall into a deep sleep. I can recover and have a better day the next day.\n\nSample 2: In my case, watching TV is the best way to get rid of stress\nNowadays I've been looking for a job. I've prepared a resume and applied for many companies but it's really hard to get a job opportunity. I mean, I hardly get a chance to have an interview. I'm really stressed out. I really don't know what to do. It's really frustrating (bực bội). But you know at night, after taking a shower, I turn on the TV. I watch many programs and my favorite program is called Running Man. It's a reality show (chương trình truyền hình thực tế) and it's really funny. I laugh a lot watching people in the show completing their missions. I feel so relaxed, and it really helps me to relieve stress. After that, I feel better and can recharge my battery to get on with my job hunting.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T10:25:50.187Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "27yt92x34-tv3u-3040-w2a7-78869uvwx992",
    "question": "Do you agree or disagree with the statement: It's a waste of time to watch TV?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I disagree that it is a waste of time to watch TV because this activity has many benefits. \nFirst, when watching TV programs, people can relax and recharge their battery after a stressful day. Also, TV programs can provide useful knowledge about science, history, culture, and so on, which would allow people to enhance their perspectives (cải thiện thế giới quan). For example, I usually watch a TV program called Follow us, which is a travel show. I can learn about a lot of different cultures around the world and since it is entertaining, I can unwind and refresh my mind after work.\n\nSample 2: I disagree that it is a waste of time to watch TV because it's helpful and educational\nFor example, I usually watch a TV program called Follow us. There are 4 people in the show. Actually they are famous singers and actors in Vietnam. They travel to different places and complete the missions. Like in last episode, they travelled to Japan. They visited many places such as Tokyo Square, Tokyo Tower and so on. Also, they went to Japanese restaurants and ate a lot of food such as sushi, ramen and so on. When I was watching it, I was able to learn about Japan and its culture. And the program was fun, I was able to get rid of stress and unwind.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T10:29:02.820Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "28zu03y45-uw4v-4151-x3b8-89970vwxy001",
    "question": "Do you prefer to live without: TV or mobile phone?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I prefer to live without mobile phone\nIt's better for my life.\nFor example, I use a smartphone all the time. I do a lot of things on my smartphone and all I have to do is using some apps. I can do shopping. I can watch videos. I can listen to music. To be honest, I spend too much time on my smartphone. Like yesterday, I wasted 7 hours watching Tiktok videos all day long. I watched one video after another. Then I played online game and chat with my friends. It was a waste of time. As a result, I couldn't do homework. I wasn't able to do housework as well. I didn't do anything productive. It was so meaningless. As you can see, I should get rid of it, I should live without my phone.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T10:32:16.453Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "29av14z56-vx5w-5262-y4c9-90081wxyza10",
    "question": "What is the best method of learning another country's culture or traditions?\nWatch TV/ Researching online/ Reading books",
    "answer": "Sample 1: Watching TV is the best method of learning another country's culture or traditions\n10 years ago, I started to watch a TV program called Friends. It is an American sitcom series. There are 5 friends in the show. They live together, they eat together, they share their lives together. And when watching this show, I was able to learn many things about American cultures, about girlfriend and boyfriend relation, their food culture. They were very helpful. On top of that, I was able to learn language cuz when I was interested in this show, I wanted to know more about what's going in so I kept on learning the expressions, words and so on. Through this program, I was able to improve my English skills and understand American cultures.\n\nSample 2: Researching online is the best method of learning another country's culture or traditions\nToday it's easier for people to do research on websites where they can find articles, videos, and so on about the cultures and traditions of a country. For example, recently I wanted to learn more about Japanese culture. I did a search (tìm kiếm) on Google to gather more information. There were many websites outlining Japanese traditional festivals, local cuisines, and famous destinations. I can also watch many videos from travel bloggers who shared their experiences living in this country.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T10:35:29.086Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "30bw25a67-wy6x-6373-z5d0-01192xyzab229",
    "question": "Do you agree or disagree that people read less now than they used to in the past during their free time?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I agree that people read less now than they used to in the past during their free time\nThere are many other ways for them to get information or entertain.\nFor example, when I was young, I loved to read books. So whenever I had free time, I went to a bookstore and bought some books to read. It was interesting because I was able to get information and secondhand experience (trải nghiệm thứ cấp). Nowadays, I don't read books anymore because I can use the Internet. I can do many things on the Internet. I can play online games, I can watch Youtube videos and I can get lots of information there. I don't turn to (tìm tới) book for entertainment or to get information.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T10:38:42.719Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "31cx36b78-xz7y-7484-a6e1-12203yzabc338",
    "question": "Do you agree or disagree: Internet news sources are less reliable than TV news programs.",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I agree that Internet news sources are less reliable than TV news programs.\nInformation contained on TV shows must undergo rigorous fact-checking progress (trải qua quy trình kiểm duyệt khắt khe) so it is reliable. By contrast, not all the news on the Internet is credible (đáng tin cậy). Many websites tend to report stories about controversial issues (vấn đề gây tranh cãi) or shocking events to gain high viewership/media traffic (câu view). Also, on social media platforms like Facebook, people can post anything and fake news is rampant. Given these, news reports on the Internet is less dependable than TV news shows.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T10:41:56.352Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "32dy47c89-ya8z-8595-b7f2-23314zabc447",
    "question": "Which is better to file a complaint: via email or phone?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: People can receive immediate response (nhận phản hồi ngay lập tức) and solve the problems more quickly and effectively\nFor example, last night I was super hungry, so I ordered fried chicken. I waited for 2 hours and received my chicken. I was starving, I ate the chicken but it was so cold. It was not delicious. I was so upset and disappointed, so I called the restaurant right away. I made a complaint. I was received their apology right away and they sent me a new chicken. When I ate it, this time it was really hot, really delicious. I was super satisfied with it. I was really happy because I was able to get something right away, solve the problem right away.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T10:45:09.985Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "33ez58d90-zb9a-9606-c8g3-34425abcde556",
    "question": "Which is the more effective form of conversation? Why?\nSpeaking face to face or speaking on the phone",
    "answer": "Sample 1: Speaking face to face is the more effective form of conversation.\nIf we interact directly with each other, we can see and respond to reactions like facial expressions and body language and their tone of voice. These elements can help avoid misunderstanding and miscommunication.\nLast year, I got a job in the marketing department. Sometimes I worked with people in Japan. At first, we didn't meet in person. We talked on the phone. We used emails to discuss work. There was a lot of miscommunication and misunderstanding. Then I went on business trips more often. I met our partners in person. We had face to face meetings. It was better for our communication. All in all, it was helpful for our work.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T10:48:23.618Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "34fa69e01-ac0b-0717-d9h4-45536bcdef665",
    "question": "Do you agree or disagree that people have become more dependent on mobile phones these days compared to the past?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I agree that people have become more dependent on mobile phones these days compared to the past\nIt makes your life convenient and useful.\nFor example, I have a smartphone. Yesterday, I stayed at home all day long and I had no food, no TV, no computers. However, I was totally fine. Because like I said, I had my smartphone with me. And on my phone, there are so many different kinds of app. I was able to use a food delivery app called Nowfood. And I was able to order breakfast, lunch and dinner. Also I used a lot of apps to entertain myself. I used Netflix app, used Youtube app. I used Facebook to communicate with my friends. Like you see, I was able to have a good day just by using my phone. I can't live without it.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T10:51:37.251Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "35gb70f12-bd1c-1828-e0i5-56647cdefg774",
    "question": "What are some good things about reading reviews of products or services written by customers?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: Reading reviews of products or services written by customers has many benefits.\nPeople tend to share their practical experiences (trải nghiệm thực tế) when buying the products or services so I can compare the price, services, and so on to make a good purchasing decision.\nLast week, I wanted to buy a dress for the year-end party. Since I was very busy, I decided to do online shopping. I used an app called Shopee and did some research. Luckily, I came across a shop with the rating of 4.9 out of 5. I read all reviews from previous customers who uploaded the picture and video of the dress. Most of them were positive so I decided to place an order (đặt đơn hàng). 2 days later, the shipment arrived and when I tried the dress, it fit me perfectly. Thanks to customer reviews, I managed to buy a nice dress.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T10:54:50.884Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "36hc81g23-ce2d-2939-f1j6-67758defgh883",
    "question": "Some people believe that it's easier for young people to make friends, others say it's easier for old people make friends. What do you think?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I think it's easier for young people to make friends because they are generally open-minded (cởi mở) to meet new people. Also, the availability of social network and electronic devices can allow the young to connect with people who have some common interest. In contrast, old people are not tech-savvy (sành công nghệ) so they may hesitate to (ngần ngại) use technology to connect with others\nI am a student. I often use social media platforms like Facebook or Instagram to meet people from all over the world. We often share moments (chia sẻ khoảnh khắc) in our lives and keep in touch with each other.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T10:58:03.517Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "37id92h34-df3e-3040-g2k7-78869efghi992",
    "question": "Do you agree with the statement 'People have more time relax now than in the past'?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I disagree that people have more time relax now than in the past \nIn the competitive world (thế giới cạnh tranh), people have to work or study hard to afford a more comfortable life (có cuộc sống thoải mái). This would leave them little time to relax.\nI am an office worker. Normally I have to work extra time to earn some money to keep up with higher living costs (theo kịp chi phí sống cao). I spend 3 days a week studying a foreign language. As a result, I hardly have free time to rest like when I was a student.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T11:01:17.150Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "38je03i45-eg4f-4151-h3l8-89970fghij001",
    "question": "Do you agree with the statement 'Mobile phones make people difficult to balance between work and life'?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I agree that mobile phones make people difficult to balance between work and life \nIt's convenient to use smartphones to connect with (kết nối) people so they make use of (tận dụng, lạm dụng) it to handle workplace issues even after work. Therefore, employees may disconnect from work (ngắt kết nối khỏi công việc) outside of office hours and suffer from (hứng chịu) work-life imbalance.\nI have been working in the sales department. Throughout the day, I receive many work-related emails, messages, and notifications on my phone. Even after I leave the office, my colleagues and clients reach out (liên hệ) with questions and updates. Sometimes, I find it hard to disconnect from work.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T11:04:30.783Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "39kf14j56-fh5g-5262-i4m9-90081ghijk110",
    "question": "Do you agree or disagree that luck is an important factor to become successful artist?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: Luck can indeed be an important factor in the success of an artist, just as it can be in various aspects of life.\nBTS, a Korean boy band, is a good example. This band was lucky to emerge (nổi lên) during a time when K-pop was gaining international recognition (nhận diện toàn cầu) and social media and online streaming platforms became popular. Also, thanks to innovative marketing strategies of their agency, they can reach (tiếp cận) a worldwide audience more easily. If there had not been timing and technology factors, they would not be successful now.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T11:07:44.416Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "40lg25k67-gi6h-6373-j5n0-01192ijklm229",
    "question": "Considering the changes happening in our society, which of the following industries do you think will change the most in the future?\nAgriculture – Entertainment - Transportation",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I think transportation will change the most in the future\nOne good change is that more people are using cars and bikes that run on renewable energy (năng lượng tái tạo). Pollution is a big problem nowadays, so it's important to use energy sources that don't produce carbon emissions. Electric cars and bikes are already available worldwide, but I think governments will make them more common and cheaper in the future. This will help reduce the use of fossil fuels (nhiên liệu hóa thạch) and improve the environment.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T11:10:58.049Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "41mh36l78-hj7i-7484-k6o1-12203jklmn338",
    "question": "Which has improved human's lives more: TV or airplane?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I believe airplanes have improved human's lives more\nThe airplane allows people to travel larger distances in shorter amounts of time. So, it's easier and more convenient for people around the world to discover different places and learn about different cultures. The increase in tourism can also benefit the country as traveling can generate more revenue (tạo doanh thu) and foster cultural exchange (thúc đẩy trao đổi văn hóa).\nAlso, with the help of airplane, we can transport products in a short time. This can promote international business.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T11:14:11.682Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "42ni47m89-ik8j-8595-l7p2-23314klmno447",
    "question": "Do you agree or disagree that advertisements encourage people to purchase unnecessary products?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I agree that advertisements encourage people to purchase unnecessary products.\nAdvertisers often use different ways to persuade and influence consumer behaviors (ảnh hưởng hành vi khách hàng). For example, they use promotion programs like buy 1 get 1 or showcase (trình bày) the unique features of products to capture consumers' attention (thu hút người tiêu dùng). So, sooner or later (sớm hay muộn), this would make customers buy the products, which could turn out (hóa ra) to be wasteful or unnecessary. For example, recently when I was surfing my Instagram, I saw an ad about a dress with 70% off. I bought right away but when I received it, I realized I already had some dresses with same style at home and I didn't wear it much.\n\nSample 2: I agree that advertisements encourage people to purchase unnecessary products\nAdvertisements often manipulate people to buy things.\nFor example, last weekend when I was watching TV, I saw an ad about new shoes. They were winter boots. Nowadays in my city, it's very cold outside. It's going to be snowy soon. I really wanted to buy those boots. They looked so comfy and trendy. The next day I went to a department store and I bought them right away. They were quite expensive, more than $500. At that time I loved them but now actually I regret I didn't need those boots because I didn't go outside much and I already had same pair of boots at home.\n\nSample 3: I disgree that advertisements encourage people to purchase unnecessary products\nIt's important for products to be advertised because otherwise, we wouldn't know what's out there, what's available. For example recently I saw an ad about air fryer. I used to cook with a frying pan in my kitchen. But when I saw this ad, it said it can save me a lot of time and energy when I'm cooking and it's much more convenient. I bought this product 2 days later and I have been using it as it's time-saving and even reduces a lot of oil for cooking.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T11:17:24.315Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "43oj58n90-jl9k-9606-m8q3-34425lmnop556",
    "question": "What are advantages of living in a big city?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: Living in a big city has many benefits. First, there are many companies in different fields based in the city so people can have more job opportunities with higher salaries, which may not be available in the countryside. Second, people can access (tiếp cận) better healthcare and education services, as most reputable (danh giá) schools and hospitals are located in this area. Finally, urban areas can offer many entertainment options such as concerts and transportation options such as metro, buses, which make citizens' lives convenient and enjoyable.\n\nSample 2: I live in a big city called Hanoi. Actually it's the capital of Vietnam so it's really big. There are many things to do and see. For example, there are many museums such as historical museums, art museums and so on. So on weekends, I like to go to a museum and enjoy the exhibition. It's a great way to learn many things and relax on weekend. Moreover, there are a lot of public transportation options so I can take the subway or bus, or I can take a taxi to go wherever I want. It's convenient. As you can see, I really enjoy living in a big city.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T11:20:37.948Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "44pk69o01-km0l-0717-n9r4-45536mnopq665",
    "question": "Which has a bigger influence on the happiness of your life?\nLocation of your house or location of your workplace",
    "answer": "Sample 1: Location of my house has a bigger influence on the happiness of my life\nA convenient location can allow me to enjoy different facilities.\nLast year I graduated from college and got a job in marketing department. There were many team projects and I was always busy. It was very stressful. Fortunately my house was located in downtown area. I can do many things after work. Sometimes I go to the museum and enjoy the exhibition. Sometimes I go to theater to watch a movie. By doing so, I can get rid of stress. In addition, there are many convenient facilities such as hospitals, public transportation and so on. So I can go wherever I want whenever I want. It's very convenient. I'm very satisfied with my life now.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T11:23:51.581Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "45ql70p12-ln1m-1828-o0s5-56647nopqr774",
    "question": "Is it better to drive a car or take a train when you go on a long trip?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: It is better to drive a car when I go on a long trip. it's convenient.\nLast month I went on a long trip. I stayed there for one month. I did many things there. I ate local food, I visited many places, I did shopping. At that time, I rented a car so I can go wherever I wanted. I didn't have to take a taxi. I didn't have to take buses or subway. It was very convenient to drive on my own. I was able to save a lot of time. As a result, I was able to enjoy more activities and more places.\n\nSample 2: It is better to take a train when I go on a long trip. \nI can do other activities instead of focusing on driving so it's more comfortable\nLast month I went on a long trip to a city in the south from the north. At that time, I was exhausted because a week before the trip, I had been working hard. While I was taking the train, I was able to sleep and rest. After 2 hours, I arrived in the city, and I stayed there for 3 days. I was able to do many things there because I was in good condition (trong điều kiện tốt). I ate local food. I visited many places. It was amazing. Because I didn't drive my car, I was able to rest and enjoy my trip to the fullest.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T11:27:05.214Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "46rm81q23-mo2n-2939-p1t6-67758opqrs883",
    "question": "Do you agree or disagree that parents should discourage their children from having celebrities such as musicians or actors as their role models? Why?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I disagree that parents should discourage their children from having celebrities such as musicians or actors as their role models (hình mẫu lý tưởng)\nIt's very helpful for children to have celebrities as their role model\nWhen I was in middle school, singer Taylor Swift released an album. It was amazing. I loved all the songs. I wanted to sing a song. I wanted to understand the lyrics so I studied English so hard. I practiced English so hard and it helped me become more musical and improve my English skills. also, she was so pretty and sexy. I wanted to be like her. I tried to follow her style. You know she was a great role model.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T11:30:18.847Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "47sn92r34-np3o-3040-q2u7-78869pqrst992",
    "question": "Do you agree or disagree that people should put a long time in order to make a good decision?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I agree that people should put a long time in order to make a good decision.\nThey can have enough time to collect more information before making an informed decision\nFor example, last year, I wanted to buy a laptop computer. My old one was too old and slow so I went to a big electronic store near my house. But there were too many models and I didn't know what to choose. So I came back home, I visited online websites. There were many reviews and lots of information online. I compared many things such as size, weight and so on. It took lots of time and effort but I did a research. After 2 months, I was able to buy a nice computer. It has been working well since I don't regret my decision.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T11:33:31.480Z"
  },
   {
    "id": "48to03s45-oq4p-4151-r3v8-89970qrstu001",
    "question": "What are some advantages of getting friends' advice when making an important decision?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: They are reliable\nLast year, I graduated from college and got a job in other city, Hanoi. I didn't know what to do because I didn't know where to live, whether to move to Hanoi was a good idea. So I talked to my friend named Tim. Actually at that time he was living in Hanoi. I asked him many questions. He gave me a lot of tips and advice and he recommended me moving to Hanoi. And I followed his advice. Now I live and work in Hanoi. I can do many things. I can learn many stuff. I'm able to broaden my perspective. Thanks to my friend, I was able to make a very good decision.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T11:36:45.113Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "49up14t56-pr5q-5262-s4w9-90081rstuv110",
    "question": "Do you agree or disagree that talent has a big influence on the success of an artist?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: I agree that talent has a big influence on the success of an artist. Without talent, it would be difficult for artists to stand out in the competitive environment. For instance, BTS, a Korean boyband, has many talents such as singing, dancing, and songwriting. Also, they have both good-looking (đẹp trai) appearance (ngoại hình) and pleasing personalities (tính cách dễ chịu) so they always leave a good impression on both the public and media, which may lead to high popularity. Thanks to their multiple talents, they could become successful in the entertainment industry.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T11:40:58.746Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "50vq25u67-qs6r-6373-t5x0-01192stuvw229",
    "question": "Should government provide tuition for college students?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: This financial support will reduce financial burden on students and motivate them to study harder\nWhen I was in college, I had to pay tuition which was very expensive. My parents weren't able to support me. So I had to work part-time job which was hard and exhausting. One day, I heard the government started providing tuition for college students. I applied for it. Luckily, I was able to get a full scholarship. Thanks to this policy, I was able to focus on my studies, I was able to finish my degree.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T11:44:12.379Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "51wr36v78-rt7s-7484-u6y1-12203tuvwx338",
    "question": "Which has a bigger influence on improving the lives of human: telephones, computers or automobiles?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: Computers have a bigger influence on improving the lives of human\nWhen I was young, to write something, I had to use a piece of paper and pen. There was a lot of work when I wanted to write things like essays, reports and so on. I had to write 3.4 pages. But nowadays I can use my computer. All I have to do is use a laptop computer, open Microsoft Word and I just type whatever I want. It's much easier. I can type long pages. It's very helpful for my study.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T11:47:26.012Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "52xs47w89-su8t-8595-v7z2-23314uvwxy447",
    "question": "Which of the following things contributes the most to your happiness?\nHaving a satisfying job\nExercising regularly\nHaving a good relationship with friends and family",
    "answer": "Sample 1: Exercising regularly. It's very important for me\nI'm a health freak and I love to exercise and I work 12 hours a day. It's quite stressful. Although I love my job, it takes a lot of my energy. That's why I'm stressed out at the end of the day. And when I come back home, I want to do yoga or sometimes I go downstairs to go to the gym. I exercise at least 5 times a week. When I exercise, I use all my energy to lift weights (nâng tạ), stretch out my body. I feel better. I feel more energetic and I am able to get rid of stress. That's what makes me happy.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T11:50:39.645Z"
  },
  {
    "id": "53yt58x90-tv9u-9606-w8a3-34425vwxyz556",
    "question": "What are disadvantages of living in a big city?",
    "answer": "Sample 1: When I was young, I lived in a small town called ND. It was a beautiful place. There were many green parks. I was able to enjoy nature. There were not many cars and people. It was very peaceful and quiet. When I went to college, I moved to Hanoi. Now, I live there. It is a big city. There are many cars and buildings. There are so many people everywhere. It is very noisy and crowded. There are not many green parks. I can't enjoy nature. It is very stressful.",
    "createdAt": "2025-04-05T11:53:53.278Z"
  }
]